Lucas William Bateson



Contact

Address:

Bekkelagsveien 20B Oslo, Norway 1177 Oslo

Phone:

+47 934 007 38

Email:

lucas.bateson@gmail.com

Languages

English – Native Norwegian – Native German – Beginner (Studied for 3 years at school)

Platforms

Github

Lucas8448

LinkedIn

Lucas Bateson

Summary

I am a 16-year-old student studying Information technology and Media production at Fyrstikkallen Vgs in Oslo, Norway. I am a dual British/Norwegian National, although I am born and raised in Oslo.

Skills

- Backend development using Python Flask.
- Vue.js/React.
- Basic Docker understanding.
- Html, CSS and JavaScript for website creation.
- Scylla/Sqlite3 database querying.

Experience

Programming teacher Aug 2020 – Jun 2021

Oslo commune, Oslo

- Responsible for helping grade 4 students learn block programming.

Scout Leader Aug 2018 - present

Oslo

- Responsible for a patrol of 10 scouts ensuring well-being and safety on trips.
- Responsible for giving guidance to patrol leaders on how to lead their patrols.
- Completed multiple courses with a focus on leadership skills.

Media production Sept 2022 – present

Jordal AMFI, Oslo

- Producing the live video replays for a media cube during multiple live hockey matches using a 3Play video capture/replay solution.
- Working as a camera operator with a professional production team.

Education

Fyrstikkallen Vgs

Aug 2022 - Present

- Information technology and media production studies

Grades

Grades range from 1-6 with 1-2 being low competence, 3-4 being medium competence, and 5-6 being high competence:

- 6 Programming, Vocational Studies, Science, Technological understanding, Production/Storytelling
- 5 English, P.E

Average: 5,75

Certifications

AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

References

Haidar Nuri - VG2 Teacher within IT at Fyrstikkalleen VGS

Email: haidar.nuri@osloskolen.no

About:

Haidar has been following my progress for over half a year and has been engaged in the projects I've been working on. Among other things, he has taught me Azure and followed my completion of the AZ-900 certification. Even though he hasn't been my teacher for the past year, he is still the one who has followed my work most closely and has deep professional understanding within my area of work. Although as of August 2023 he is my form teacher.

Hobbies

Scouts, Skiing, Online gaming, Microelectronics and Programming